惊世狂花
[ 女人#1 ] 你的身影总是浮现在我脑海里
I had this image of you inside of me...
象是我的一部分
like a part of me.
[ 女人#2 ] 你计划了这整件事.
You planned this whole thing.
[ 女人#1 ] 我们樽约核做的决定付出代价
We make our own choice. We pay our own prices.
[ 女人#2 ] 五年的时间不短啊
Five years is a long time.
[ 男人] 他妈的, 钱到底在那?
Where's the fuckin' money?
[ 女人#1 ] 全部的生意.
All part of the business.
[ 男人 ] 全部的生意.
[ 女人#1 ] 你曾经做过个选择
You made a choice once.
[ 女人#2 ] 什么选择?
What choice?
[ 女人#1 ] 我要离开.
I want out.
[ 女人#1 ]就象我的一部分
Like a part of me.
[ 女人 ] 把电梯停住.
Hold the elevator.
谢了.
Thanks.
是的老板, 我已经全查过一扁了
Yeah, I looked over everything, sir.
我不觉得那里会有什么问题
I don't think there should be any problems.
是老板, 我整理了那些桶并且查过了浴室
Yes, sir, I ordered the vanity and I looked at the tub.
我很快就能搞定的
I'm pretty sure we can rout it out.
[ 低沉的呻吟声 ]
好的, 我明天会由这一切东西开始着手
Yeah, I'll start everything first thing tomorrow.
[ 呻吟声持续着 ]
卞齐倪先生, 再次多谢你给了我这个机会.
Thanks again for this opportunity, Mr. Bianchini.
[ 叹气 ] 是啊.
Yeah.
[ 呻吟声渐渐变大 ]
[ 吵杂的撞击声 ]
[ 敲门声 ]
嗨.
Hi.
我是维雅乐. 我们在电梯里见过面了.
My name is Violet. We sort of met on the elevator.
我叫克尔奇.
I'm Corky.
听说你在这儿上班, 所以我想...
I heard you working in here, and I was wondering...
请你喝杯咖啡.
if you'd like a cup of coffee.
好啊.
Sure.
请进来.
Come on in.
等我一下.
Just give me a second.
好的.
All right.
拉吉夫怎么了?
What happened to Rajiv?
他回去印度或其他地方了, 但是不久就会回来了.
He went home to India or someplace, but I think he'll be back.
那你这份工只是暂时性的?
So this is just a temporary situation for you?
是啊, 大概是那样. 一天一次.
Yeah, pretty much. One day at a time.
我觉得你是个耿直的人.
I guessed you're a straight black.
猜的不错.
Good guess.
谢谢.
Thanks.
不客气.
My pleasure.
老实说, 我是有个隐藏动机.
To be honest, I did have a slightly ulterior motive.
我在想不知道可不可以请你帮个忙.
I was wondering if I might ask you a little favor.
帮忙.  是啊.
Favor.   Yeah.
我是个过惯夜生活的人, 所以我想...
I'm kind of a night person, and I was wondering...
不知道你能不能等迟一些再用你那强力的工具.
if you might wait a little bit before you start using the power tools.
啊, 对不起.  嗯, 没关系. 没关系.
Oh, sorry.   Oh, no. No.
不是你的错. 实在是这里的墙壁太薄了.
It's not your fault. It's just the walls here are so terribly thin.
真的.  就象是在同一间房似的.
Really.   It's like you're in the same room.
可是如果那太麻烦的话就没关系啦.
If it's too much trouble, I understand.
啊不麻烦. 我还有其他的事情可以做.
It's no trouble at all. I got a lot to do here.
这些全是你一人的工作?
You doin' all the work yourself?
太令人敬佩了.
That is so amazing.
我很佩服那些善于修理东西的人.
I am so in awe of people who can fix things.
我爸也是那样. 我们从没买过新的东西.
My dad was like that. We never had anything new.
每当有东西坏了, 他就会...
Whenever anything was broken, he would just...
把它打开来, 弄一弄看...
open it up, tinker with it a little bit...
再把它修好.
and fix it.
他有一双很巧的手.
His hands were magic.
我敢打赌, 你这汽车有20年了吧.
I'll bet your car is 20 years old.
货车.
Truck.
哦, 是的, 货车.
Truck. Of course.
'63年次的 彻维.  我就知道.
'63 Chevy.   I knew it.
嗯, 我觉得我该走了.
Well, I guess I should be going.
你有空的话可以随时过来.
You can drop the cup off at any time.
谢了.
Thanks.
不客气.
My pleasure.
叮 叮  [ 点播机在播放着蓝调 ]
叮 你真不应该啊 常常让女人伤心 叮  呵呵.
Well, well.
好久不见了, 克尔奇.  叮 叮 [ 持续着 ]
It's been a long time, Cork.
五年, 二个月十六天.
Five years, two months and sixteen days.
你过的怎样啊, 苏?  惨死了.
How you doin', Sue?   Like shit.
既然我们又见面了, 请你喝杯东西.
Now that we're all caught up, can I buy you a drink?
谢谢.
Thanks.
叮 朋友们一直说 叮  欢迎回来.
*  Friends keep tellin' me *   Welcome home.
叮 说你的坏话 叮
*  That you ain't no good *
叮 不过, 唉, 唉, 他们都不了解 叮
*  But, oh, oh, they don't know *
你找到工作了吗?
Did you get a job yet?
有. 一些通水喉, 画画 之类的.
Yeah. Some plumbing, painting and shit.
我是指 工作. 一个真正的工作.
I mean a J O B. A real job.
不了, 不适合我啊, 苏.
No. Not for me, Sue.
我只是来这找人上床
I'm just here to get laid.
叮 我不会在 叮
*  I ain't never gonna *
叮 爱上男人了 叮
*  Love a man *
叮 我那样的 叮
*  The way that I *
叮 爱着你 叮
*  I love you *
叮 很久以前, 我以为 叮
*  Some time ago I thought *
叮 你不适合我 叮
*  You had run out of fools *
叮 可是我错了 叮
*  But I was so wrong *
叮叮 [ 持续着 ]
嗨.  哈罗.
Hi.   Hello.
哎 洁西, 发生什么事了?
Hey, Jesse, what's happenin' here?
等等. 我认识你.
Wait. I know you.
哦? 我不觉得.
I don't think so.
我不知道你被放出来了
I didn't know you were out.
当你对卡尼与莱喜感到厌倦时, 来找我吧.
When you get tired of Cagney and Lacey, find me.
叮 你千万千万别跟我说我们之间没了 叮
*  Don't you never never say that we're through *
[ 弹动东西声 ]
[ 弹动声持续着 ]
叮叮 [ 摇滚乐声 ]
叮 快与慢  夜与昼 叮
*  Fast and slow Night and day *
叮 当你停止思考 叮
*  When you stop to think *
叮 它就突然出现 叮
*  It just gets in the way *
叮 我们之间没有阻碍 叮
*  And there's not a single soul among us *
[ 电话铃声 ]
喂.
Yeah.
哦 卞齐倪先生
Hey, Mr. Bianchini.
一切都进行的很顺利
Everything's going just fine.
是的 我把浴缸清理了
Yeah, I got the tub drain all cleaned out.
什么房间?
What apartment?
噢 不是的
Oh, no.
天! 我没想到他会打给你.
Shit! I didn't know he would call you.
你一定觉得我很烦.
You must think I'm a total nuisance.
也不尽然啦.
Not exactly.
对不起, 我通常都是找拉吉夫来...
I'm sorry. I would usually call Rajiv...
可是现在我不知道该怎么办, 所以只好打给卞齐倪先生.
but I didn't know what to do, so I called Mr. Bianchini.
他说你丢了些东西?  是的.
He said you lost something?   Yeah.
进来吧.
Come on in.
我洗碗后放掉水时不小心把耳环掉下去了.
I was doing the dishes, and just as I pulled the stopper, my earring fell in.
所以我现在很沮丧. 那是我最喜欢的东西之一啊.
That's why I got upset. It's one of my favorites.
你有没有个锅或者桶?
You got a pot or a bucket?
[ 扭水喉声 ]
[ 扭水喉声, 水流声 ]
找到了吗?
Did you find it?
哦 天啊, 我真不敢相信.
Oh, my God. I can't believe that.
我太感激你了. 不知道怎样才能报答你啊.
I can't thank you enough. You have to let me pay you something.
不必了.  不必?
No.   No ?
告诉卞齐倪我会做的, 是我干的.
Told Bianchini I'd do it. I did it.
如果你不想收钱的话, 请你喝杯东西如何?
If you won't take money, how about a drink?
你不可能整个晚上都在忙的吧.
You can't work all night.
好吧.
All right.
就一杯.
One drink.
你想要喝点什么?
What would you like?
啤酒.
Beer.
当然.
Of course.
坐吧.
Sit down.
谢了.
Thanks.
你看起来不太舒服.
You seem uncomfortable.
是不是因为我而紧张啊, 克尔奇?
Do I make you nervous, Corky?
不是.
No.
也许是口渴.
Thirsty, maybe.
也许是好奇.
Curious, maybe.
真有趣. 我自己觉得有点好奇呢.
That's funny. I'm feeling a little bit curious myself.
真棒的纹身.
That's a great tattoo.
真漂亮的战斧
Beautiful labris.
我知道那是什么你是不是很惊讶?
Are you surprised I know what it is?
也许吧.
Maybe.
我也有纹身.
I have a tattoo.
有没有兴趣看看啊?
Would you like to see it?
一个在纽约市区附近的女人帮我纹的.
A woman in upstate New York did it for me.
你喜欢吗?
Do you like it?
她花了一整天的功夫弄的.
Took her all day to do it.
她担保说不会疼的, 可是...
She promised it wouIdn't hurt, but...
我还是痛了好一阵子.
it was sore for a long time after.
连轻轻摸都会疼.
I couldn't even touch it.
可现在我喜欢摸上去的感觉.
Now I love the way it feels.
这里.
Here.
摸摸看.
Touch it.
你在干嘛?  你看不出来?
What are you doing?   Isn't it obvious?
我在引诱你.
I'm trying to seduce you.
为什么?
Why?
因为我想要你.
Because I want to.
当天在电梯里头碰面时我就已经想要你了.
I've wanted to ever since I saw you that day in the elevator.
我知道你可能不相信...
I know you don't believe me...
但是我可以证明给你看.
but I can prove it to you.
你将不会相信你接下来所看到的
You can't believe what you'd see...
但是你能够相信你所能感觉到的.
but you can believe what you feel.
自那天起我无时无刻都在想着你.
I've been thinking about you all day.
[ 喘气, 呻吟 ]
这整件事是个圈套.
You planned this whole thing.
你故意把耳环丢进洗手盆的, 对吧?
You dropped that earring down the sink on purpose, didn't you?
如果我说是的话, 你会不会就把手拿开了?
If I say yes, will you take your hand away?
不会.  是的.
No.   Yes.
噢, 啊, 克尔奇.
Oh, please, Corky.
噢, 啊.
Oh, please.
吻我!
Kiss me!
[ 喘气声持续着 ]
[ 开门声 ]  哦, 他妈的!
Oh, fuck!
维雅乐! 维, 你在家吗?
Violet! Vi, you home?
在, 我在这儿, 凯
Yeah, I'm right here, C.
这是什么?  我没有
What the fuck is this?   I didn't
这是什么混账
What the fuck is
哦.
Oh.
克尔奇, 这位是凯撒. 凯撒, 克尔奇.
Corky, this is Caesar. Caesar, Corky.
[ 笑声 ] 我以为
I thought
这里真他妈的暗.
It's fuckin' dark in here.
克尔奇在帮卞齐倪先生办事.
Corky's doing some work for Mr. Bianchini.
哦, 真的, 嗯. 别跟我说那些.
Oh, yeah. Right. Don mentioned that to me.
对不起, 嗨.
I'm sorry. Hi.
欢迎你加入这个家族.
Welcome to the family.
你, 跟拉吉夫一起上班, 对吧?
So you're working with Rajiv, right?
不, 拉吉夫在印度.
No. Rajiv's in India.
她自己一个人做工.
She's doing the work herself.
哦, 是这样.
No shit.
卞齐倪请了你. 那你的手艺肯定不错.
Bianchini hired you. You must be pretty good with your hands.
他是我的好朋友.  维雅乐也是这么说的.
He's a good friend of mine.   That's what Violet says.
正确来说是家族.
Family really.
你什么时候被放出来的?  老天, 凯撒.
When did you get out?   Jesus, Caesar.
啥? 那又不是什么大不了的.
What? It ain't no big fuckin' deal.
我知道阿当雇佣的人.
I know who Don hires.
你知道的, 他自己也被抓过. 十三年了.
You know, he did time himself. Thirteen fuckin' years.
你呢? 多久?
What did you do?
五.  五.
Five.   Five.
那不坏啊. 因为什么事被抓?
That's not bad. What for?
那根本都不关你事.
That's none of your goddamn business.
你们俩都说的对, 根本不关我事.
You're right. She's right. It's none of my goddamn business.
你可以不必告诉我. 只是
You don't have to tell me. It's just
我只想告诉你一件事, 好吗?
I want you to understand one thing, all right?
你是这里少数的好人之一.
You're amongst good people here.
来吧, 来吧.
Come on, come on.
假如你了解我说什么的话, 你会收下这钱的.
If you understand what I'm talkin' about, you'll take the money.
否则我真的为你担心了.
If you don't, then I'm gonna have to worry about you.
很好. 我不喜欢担心别人.
Good. I hate to worry.
我长了口疮.
I got ulcers.
我看我还是应该走了.
I should be going.
啥? 不行, 留下来. 请她喝东西.
What? No, stick around. Get her a drink.
我还得回去清理刷子.
I gotta go clean out my brushes.
下次吧.
Another time.
好. 下次.
Right. Another time.
唔, 克尔奇, 克尔奇. 你在干嘛?
Mmm, Corky, Corky. What are you doing?
我想见你.
I had to see you.
呃. 我不觉得那是个好主意.
Look. I don't think this is a good idea.
我想跟你道歉.
I wanted to apologize.
不, 千万别道歉.
No, please, don't apologize.
如果有什么是我所不能忍受的事, 那就是女人为了性爱而道歉.
If there's one thing I can't stand it's woman who apologize for wanting sex.
我不是为了我所做的而道歉.
I'm not apologizing for what I did.
我是为了我所没做的而道歉.
I'm apologizing for what I didn't do.
你知道那里有床吗?
You have a bed somewhere?
[ 呻吟 ]
[ 喘气 ]
[ 呻吟, 喘气持续着 ]
我的视力恢复了.
I can see again.
我正需要它.
I needed that.
那 凯撒是黑社会吗?
So Caesar's Mafia, huh?
还需要问吗?
You have to ask?
不.
No.
有趣.
Funny.
好久没人那么叫了.
Nobody really calls it that anymore.
凯撒只称它为 "生意".
Caesar just calls it "the business."
你怎么与见他的?
How did you meet him?
他们接管一间夜总会, 我当时在那里上班.
They took over a club I was working at.
凯撒当时是主管.
Caesar started managing it.
他帮人洗黑钱?  基本上是.
He's a launderer?   Basically.
你跟他在一起多久了?
How long you been with him?
大概五年了.
About five years.
五年不短啊.
Five years is a long time.
是啊.
Yes, it is.
财富的重新分配.
The redistribution of wealth.
那不是你所想知道的吗?
Excuse me?   Isn't it what you wanted to know?
我为什么被抓?
What I did time for?
"财富的重新分配."?
"The redistribution of wealth?"
那是我一向说来骗人上床的.
That's what I tell someone when I'm trying to get them in my bed.
可是我已经在你床上了.
But I'm already in your bed.
我狱里的朋友说她花时间被抓.
My cell mate would say she did her time for getting caught.
她一向比我诚实多了.
She was always a lot more honest than me.
你假如不愿意的话可以不必告诉我.
You didn't have to tell me if you didn't want to.
我想我愿意.
I guess I wanted to.
我很高兴你这么做.
I'm glad you did.
我也是.
So am I.
叮 让我告诉你我所认识的一个女孩 叮
*  Let me tell you about a girl I know *
叮 她是我的宝贝并且住在我隔壁 叮
*  She is my baby and she lives next door *
叮 每天早上太阳没出来前 叮
*  Every mornin' before the sun comes up *
叮 她用我最爱的杯子泡咖啡给我 叮
*  She brings my coffee in my favorite cup *
叮 我就是那样才知道的... 叮  你以为我不知道?
*  That's why I know... *   You think I don't know that?
噢, 别这样.
Please. Come on.
你可以 我今晚得离开.
Will you just   I have to leave tonight.
我求求你, 维雅乐.
Don't make me beg, Violet.
两分钟. 谢谢.
Two minutes. Thank you.
[ 开琐声 ]
[ 敲门声 ]  [ 开门声 ]
喂, 维雅乐.
Hey, Violet.
你今天气色不错.
You look great.
[ 低沉的呻吟 ]
[ 维雅乐 ] 你的身影一直在我脑海里.
I had this image of you inside of me.
象是我的一部分.
Like a part of me.
你是如此的美丽.
You are so beautiful.
怎么了?  没事.
What's wrong?   Nothing.
不, 你有事的. 你不想见我是不是?
Yes, there is. You didn't want to see me, did you?
我很难能忍受我自己跟一个女人睡了后...
If there's one thing I can't stand about sleeping with women...
我就开始胡思乱想.
it's all the fucking mind reading.
我不知道.  我懂的, 维雅乐.
I don't understand.   I know, Violet.
那是因为你不会了解的, 我们是不同的.
That's 'cause you can't understand. We're different.
我们没那么不同, 克尔奇.
We're not that different, Corky.
啊, 拭目以待吧.
Ah, let's see.
现在, 你该告诉我...
This is the part where you tell me...
你心里有什么烦恼...
what matters is on the inside...
还是你心理有个我的影子.
and that inside of you there's a little dyke just like me.
不, 她不象你. 她比你聪明的多了.
No, she's nothing like you. She's a whole lot smarter than you are.
她爸爸跟她说了什么?
Is that what her daddy tells her?
我知道我是谁. 用不着把它纹在肩膀上.
I know what I am. I don't have to have it tattooed on my shoulder.
你是说你不跟男人上床?  我不啊.
You saying you don't have sex with men?   I don't.
[ 冷笑 ]
天啊, 我听到了. 墙壁很薄, 记得吗?
For Christ's sake, I heard you. Thin walls, remember?
你听到的不是性爱.
What you heard wasn't sex.
那是什么?
What was it?
工作.
Work.
生命中总有得付出的选择.
You made certain choices in your life that you paid for.
你说你干这行是因为你很在行...
You said you made them because you were good at something...
并且容易.
and it was easy.
我对我这行也很在行.
You think you're the only person that's good at something?
我们为自己做的选择付出代价
We make our own choices. We pay our own prices.
虽然你不想承认, 我觉得我们很多地方很相似
I think we're more alike than you care to admit.
那今天早上那个男的呢?
What about that guy this morning?
雪丽?
Shelly?
别告诉我, 你真是个工作狂.
Don't tell me. You're a workaholic.
不是的, 雪丽知道我是怎么样的一个人. 他见到我跟另一个女人在酒吧里.
No, Shelly knows what I am. He saw me in a bar with another woman.
哦, 那么他纯粹只想看看.
Yeah. I suppose he just wants to watch.
去你的. 你马上跟我离开.
Fuck it. I think you'd better leave.
是的, 我想也是时候离开了.
Yeah, I think I'd better.
离开时别偷走任何东西.
Try not to steal anything on the way out.
[ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 你他妈的这是什么?
Where the fuck is it?
[ 隔墙的男人#2 ] 不是我做的! 我可以发誓!
I didn't do it! I swear to you!
[ 撞击声 ]
[ 隔墙的男人#2 ] 相信我吧!
Come on!
[ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 东西在那?  [ 撞击声 ]
Where is it?
[ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 哦, 痛不痛啊?  [ 隔墙的男人#2 ] 啊!
Oh, that hurt, didn't it?   Ow!
[ 撞击声持续着 ]  [ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 你以为你骗得了我?
You think you're smart?
[ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 你到底把钱藏到哪去了?
Where's that fuckin' money?
[ 隔墙的男人#2 ] 住手, 住手!
Please, please!
求求你, 放过我吧!
Please, let me go!
住手啊! [ 惊叫声 ]
Please stop it!
[ 隔墙的男人#1 ] 别逼我做我不想做的事!
Don't make me beg!
住手! 求求你!
Stop it! Please!
住手!  想耍我们? 真有种, 耍我?
Please stop!   Tryin' to fuck us? You wanna fuck me?
你个烂货. 让我送你归西.
You piece of shit. We're goin' home.
没人可以耍他!  我没有在耍他啊!
Nobody fucks him!   I'm not fucking him!
我可以向天发誓!
I swear to God!
强尼! 喂!
Johnnie! Ho!
他太吵了.
He's making too much noise.
听见没婊子? 闭嘴.
You hear that, bitch? Shut up.
给我条毛巾.
Give me a towel.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
拿去.
Here.
塞住他的嘴.
Put it in his mouth.
凯撒, 我走了.
Caesar, I'm leaving.
啥? 为什么要走?
What? Why?
真是的, 该用条更好的毛巾.  凯撒, 我是认真的.
I didn't use a good towel.   Caesar, I'm serious.
我受不了了. 我要离开.
I can't take this. I have to get out of here.
为什么?
Why?
因为你认识他?
'Cause you know him?
啊, 懂了吧?
Aw, you see?
宝贝, 我迷的就是你这点.
Baby, that's what I love about you.
你太他妈敏感了.
You're so fuckin' sensitive.
可是我喜欢你在我身边.
But I like you here.
我要你留下来.
I want you to stay.
这真叫我为难.
This is hard on me too.
我喜欢雪丽.
I like Shelly.
你去看看电视节目或者听听录音带吧
So why don't you watch some TV and put on a cassette or something?
没事吧, 维雅乐?
You okay, Violet?
米奇, 强尼在这干嘛?
Mick, why is Johnnie here?
你知道我对那神经病有多反感吗?
You know how I feel about that psycho fuck?
凯撒, 你帮我拿的东西呢?
Caesar, didn't I tell you to get something?
哦, 我忘了. 这就去.
Sure. Sorry about that.
你不该看到这一切的.
You shouldn't have to see this.
一起出去走走吧?
Why don't you get out of here? Go for a walk.
凯撒要我留下来.
Caesar wants me to stay.
别担心他, 让我来搞定.
Don't worry about Caesar. I'll handle Caesar.
走开.
Get out of here.
[ 强尼 ] 让我们彻夜狂欢吧.  好的.
We can go all night, bitch.   Okay.
谢谢你, 米奇.
Thank you, Mickey.
[ 咒骂声 ]
喏, 去吧.
Here you go.
彻夜狂欢呐! 爽啊!
All fuckin' night, baby! All night!
[ 咒骂声持续 ]
放松点吧, 强尼, 好吗?
Hey, Johnnie, ease up, okay?
婊子!
Bitch!
拉他起来.
Pick him up.
雪丽,
Shelly,
我只会问你十次, 了解吗?
I'm gonna ask you ten times. You understand?
十次.
Ten times.
是的 [ 笑声 ]
Yeah.
一. 钱在那里?
One. Where's our money?
[ 尖叫声 ]  [ 剪指头声 ]
[ 低沉惊叫声 ]
[ 叹气声 ]
你还好吧?
You all right?
走吧. 咱们离开吧.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
[ 冷笑 ] 继续.
Keep it.
雪丽在凯撒的生意上做了手脚.
Shelly was skimming from the business.
他怕凯撒发现所以来找我帮忙.
He came to see me yesterday because he was afraid Caesar found out.
他想我跟他一起逃离这里.
He wanted to run, but he wanted me to come with him.
他知道你的背景吗?
Even though he knew about you.
是的.  哦, 那他爱上你了?
Yeah.   This guy's in love with you?
他是这么说, 可我觉得不是.
That's what he tells himself, but it's not even about me.
他有很多逃走的机会, 可是他偏不走.
He could have run at any time, but he didn't want out.
听起来象是他故意被抓的样子.
It sounds like he wanted to get caught.
嗯, 可能他是故意的.
Yeah. Maybe he did.
他常跟我吹牛.
He would brag to me all the time.
说他从没怕过凯撒, 因为...
He was never afraid of Caesar because...
他不了解他.
he didn't know him.
我也不了解.
Not like I do.
我以前能够撑的住的.
I used to be able to block it out.
或者是我一直在欺骗我自己...
Or I'd just tell myself that...
说一切都是幻觉, 所以...
I wasn't really there, and so...
一点事情都没有.
none of it really mattered.
可是现在我办不到了.
But I can't do that anymore.
我在重复着雪丽的错误.
I'm making the same mistake Shelly made...
但我终于知道我需要的是什么了.
but now I know what I want.
我要离开.
I want out.
我要一个新的生活.
I want a new life.
我终于知道我要的是什么, 可是我一个人办不到.
I see what I've been waiting for, but I can't do it alone.
我需要你的帮忙, 克尔奇.
I need your help, Corky.
凯撒会去取钱, 他将会把钱  多少钱?
Caesar's gonna get the money     How much money?
雪丽说超过二百万.
Shelly said it's over two million dollars.
对啊. 那凯撒将会拿那二百万.
Yeah. So Caesar's gonna get it.
他会把钱拿去公寓那里. 然后他会点算钱.
He's gonna bring it by the apartment. He's gonna count it.
他将会查每本帐簿来了解雪丽是怎么做的手脚.
He's gonna go through the books and try and figure out how Shelly did it.
等等. 维雅乐, 你知不知道你在说什么?
Wait a minute. Violet, do you know what you're saying?
你要我帮你抢黑帮的钱?
You're asking me to help you fuck over the Mob.
维雅乐, 他们不是好惹的.
Violet, these people are serious.
假如你不了解就去问雪丽好了.
You wanna know how serious? Ask your friend Shelly.
他们比警察还利害,他们很有钱, 不怕法律.
They're worse than any cop because they have lots of money and no rules.
你要跟他们对着干, 需要有万全的计划.
You fuck them, you better do it right.
所以我要你帮忙啊. 你说你很利害的.
That's why I need your help. You said you were good.
我是利害.
I am good.
好那么现在假如我相信你说的一切.
Let's just say for a moment I believe everything you're saying.
你觉得我在说谎?  我没那样说.
You think I'm lying?   I didn't say that.
可是你有, 假设你有吧.
But since you did, let's say you are.
你要算计雪丽其实是很容易的.
It would have been easy for you to set up Shelly.
差点让他被杀了...
You could have had him killed...
你知道凯撒会把钱拿回公寓去的.
knowing that Caesar would bring the money back to the apartment.
你只是需要一个豪无干系的人来证明你的清白.
All you would need to keep yourself clean is someone unconnected.
好比说我.
Someone like me.
你真的是那样想的?
Is that what you think?
我只是假设一下.
I'm just making a point.
你完全不了解...
You have no idea what you're asking...
两个人干这种事需要多少的互相信任.
how much trust it takes two people to do something like this.
对于我来说, 偷窃跟性爱差不多.
For me, stealing has always been a lot like sex.
两个人要同样的东西.
Two people who want the same thing.
他们走进一间房, 开始讨论.
They get in a room, they talk about it.
当他们开始计划时, 好比调情一样.
They start to plan. It's like flirting.
就象是前奏一般.
It's kind of like foreplay.
因为讲的越多, 他们就越兴奋.
Because the more they talk about it, the wetter they get.
唯一不同的是, 我可以随意跟人上床.
The only difference is, I can fuck someone I've just met.
可是计划偷东西的话, 我得要一个我非常了解的人.
But to steal, I need to know someone like I know myself.
你觉得你够了解我了吗?
You think you know me like that?
我要看看那些钱.
I wanna see the money.
喔, 老天!
Oh, my God!
别担心. 不是我的.
Don't worry. It ain't mine.
凯撒, 怎么了?  真是难以置信啊, 维.
Caesar, what happened?   It was unbelievable, Vi.
真他妈的难以置信!
Un fuckin' believable!
妈的! 看看这件衣服.
Shit! Look at this shirt.
你看看. 不能用了.
Look at it. It's ruined.
这一切都是当雪丽带我们去看钱时开始的.
It all started when Shelly took us to the money.
我跟你说啊米奇, 他真不是盖的.
I'll tell you something. Mickey, he knows his shit.
他真行. 让雪丽带我们去到了那里.
He does. Shelly took us right there.
然后他跪了下来, 嗯...
So Shelly's down on his knees, right...
从地上的一个保险箱里拿出了这些钱...
and he's pulling out this money from a safe on the floor...
我当时在那...就站在那里...
and I'm standin' there...
傻...傻呼呼的看着那些钱, 你知道吗?
and I'm lookin' at it, right?
象是在说,"太爽了!"
Like, "Holy fuck!"
我当时只想到, "他是怎么办到的," 然后枪声响了!
All I can think about is, "How the fuck was he able to do this," when bang!
强尼射了他. 他杀了雪丽!
Johnny caps him. He caps Shelly!
血溅的到处都是. 溅了我一身. 钱上也全是血.
Blood goes flyin' everywhere. All over me. All over the money.
我脑子一片空白. 不知道他开了多少枪.
I have no idea if this is even all of it.
然后我冲出去就是一拳!
And right then, I go through the roof and bam!
我打了那个狗娘养的.
I punch the dumb son of a bitch.
我对着他那张傻脸用力的打下去.
I punch him right in his dumb fuckin' face.
当时我根本不理会他是谁的儿子.
I didn't give a shit whose son he was.
我只想着继续揍他揍醒这狗娘养的傻小子!
I just wanted to hit him again   smack some sense into the dumb son of a bitch!
看看我现在得面对这糟糕的处境!
Look at the shit that I gotta fuckin' deal with now!
你现在想怎么办呢?  我叫他直接照平时那样办.
What are you gonna do with it?   I told him to run it through the cycle.
可是, 强尼打给他老头子, 我觉得他有其他的计划...
But no, Johnnie calls up the old man, and I guess he's got other plans...
他明天晚上才要这些东西
because he wants to pick up this shit tomorrow night.
洗衣服的清洁剂在那?
Where's the laundry detergent?
在床单柜理.
It's in the linen cabinet.
[ 水滴声 ]
记得明天一大早到我那去.
Come to my place in the morning, early.
[ 维雅乐 ] 你觉得你够了解我了吗?
You think you know me like that?
[ 克尔奇 ] 二百万.
Two million dollars.
[ 维雅乐 ] 你终于重新考虑了.
You're having second thoughts.
不.
No.
你说凯撒洗了那些钱?
You said Caesar washed the money?
是啊.  然后呢? 说清楚点.
Yeah.   Then what? Exactly.
他把钱吊起来.  他什么?
He hung it up.   He what?
把钱弄干啊.
To let it dry.
看起来象梦境一般.
It was unreal.
到处都是晾干的百元大钞, 好象树叶那么多.
Hundreds paper clipped everywhere like leaves.
[ 熨斗声 ]
然后他再一张一张熨直.
Then one by one he ironed all of it.
[ 熨斗声持续着 ]
他没睡着?  没有, 连我也没睡.
Did he sleep?   No, but neither did I.
整个晚上我都被那声音烦着.
All night long I listened to that sound.
什么声音?  钱的声音.
What sound?   The sound of money.
[ 数钞票声 ]
那些钱现在在哪呢?
Where is it now?
在他办公室里.
It's in his office.
我今天早上见到的.
I saw it this morning.
我要去买点东西.
I need to go to the store.
钱就在他桌上的公事包里.
It's in a case on his desk.
公事包上了琐吗?
Does the case lock?
嗯.
Yes.
噢. 告诉我关于强尼的事.  强尼?
Huh. Tell me about Johnnie.   Johnnie?
我觉得他跟凯撒不太喜欢对方.
Sounds like he and Caesar don't like each other.
当然了, 他们简直是痛恨对方.
Like each other? They hate each other.
为什么?  我怎么知道.
Why?   I don't know.
那是在我还没来之前就发生的事.
Happened long before I came around.
不过我想应该是凯撒觉得强尼是个傻瓜...
I think it's basically Caesar thinks Johnnie's a complete idiot...
要换成你是凯撒, 又能怎样?
but, you know, what can you do?
那个傻瓜掌管着芝加哥, 吉诺可是他老爸啊.
Johnnie runs Chicago 'cause Gino's his father.
谁是吉诺?
Who's Gino?
吉诺 麻钟尼.
Gino Marzzone.
麻钟尼, 你是指安吉罗麻钟尼, 麻钟尼家族的首领?
Marzzone, as in Angelo Marzzone, head of the Marzzone family?
是啊, 那是他哥哥.
Yeah, that's his brother.
天呐.
Shit.
吉诺麻钟尼 今晚会到你的地方来拿钱?
Gino Marzzone's coming to your place tonight to pick up the money?
是啊.
Yeah.
而那个强尼麻钟尼是他儿子? 就是那个强尼?
And Johnnie Marzzone's his son? That's Johnnie?
是啊.
Yeah.
我的老天爷.
Sweet Jesus.
太完美了.
It's perfect.
吉诺麻尔钟今晚到你的地方去. 这很重要.
Gino Marzzone's coming to your place tonight. This is a big deal.
凯撒会很小心翼翼的应付他. 他是怕吉诺的.
Caesar's gonna want to do it right. He won't want to look like an idiot.
吉诺曾经去过你那吗?  有, 两次.
Has Gino been to your place before?   Yeah, twice.
当时怎样?  凯撒紧张的要死.
What happened?   Caesar was really nervous.
他不停的在清理房间.
He kept cleaning the apartment.
他第一次帮我挑选裙子来穿就是那时.
The first time he picked out the dress he wanted me to wear.
强尼对你有意思吗?
Did Johnnie ever hit on you?
他经常抛媚眼给我. 只要是女人他都有兴趣.
Johnnie hits on me all the time. He hits on anything in high heels.
凯撒知不知道?  他经常在凯撒面前那样做.
Did Caesar ever see this?   He does it right in front of him.
事情越来越有趣了. 接着说.
This is getting better and better. Go on.
嗯, 吉诺不太会说英文, 但是也有可能在装蒜...
Well, Gino doesn't speak much English, or at least he pretends not to...
所以他常常一见面就开门见山.
so he usually gets right to the point.
那两次他们都只聊了五分钟左右.
Both times they only talked for about five minutes.
喝了些酒就离开了.
They had a drink and then they left.
吉诺喝了些什么?  思考兹.
What did Gino drink?   Scotch.
葛莱恩李维特. 我记的那么清楚因为凯撒对那这酒很紧张.
Glenlivet. I remember that 'cause Caesar made a big deal about it.
嗯 好.
All right.
我有了个可行的好主意.
I have an idea how to make this work.
[ 克尔奇 ] 回去准备准备. 慢慢来, 做的逼真点.
Go back and get ready. Take your time. Make it real.
他们大概几点会到?
What time did you say they'd be there?
[ 维雅乐 ] 飞机 7:00 到, 所以应该是 8:00.
The plane gets in at 7:00, so I'd say around 8:00.
[ 哈欠声 ]  [ 克尔奇 ] 好吧.
All right.
凯撒应该会在某些睡醒.
Now, at some point, Caesar's gonna quit.
大概 6:00 左右吧, 让他慢慢准备.
I guess sometime around 6:00, making sure he's got time to get ready.
当他准备好后, 你就开始骗他喝酒.
As soon as he's done, you'll be there to put a big drink in his hand.
[ 凯撒 ] 雪丽做出了真让人难以置信的事.
Unbelievable what this guy Shelly did.
我告诉你哦, 雪丽真是个聪明的混蛋.
I'll tell you, Shelly's one smart ass motherfucker.
噢, 曾经是个聪明的王八蛋.
I mean, he was one smart ass motherfucker.
可怜的家伙. 辛辛苦苦工作了这么久.
Poor boy. Has to work so hard.
[ 呻吟 ]
[ 克尔奇 ] 你要让他放松, 忘了紧张.
You want him to relax, unwind.
你看起来真可爱.
You look good enough to eat.
[ 维雅乐 ] 你到时候会在哪儿?
Where will you be?
[ 克尔奇 ] 我就在隔壁房等着.
I'll be waiting in the apartment next door.
[ 维雅乐 ] 等什么?  [ 克尔奇 ] 洗澡.
Waiting for what?   For the shower.
那就是我们的暗号.
That's gonna be our signal.
当他洗完澡后, 你就去吧台那边.
When he's done with his shower, you'll go to the bar.
拿那瓶吉诺喝的思考兹.
You'll get out the scotch that Gino drinks.
那瓶酒会不小心的从你手里滑掉.
As you do, the bottle will slip from your hands.
一个意外.
An accident.
[ 凯撒 ] 维, 什么声音?
Vi, what the hell was that?
维, 听见了没?
Vi, you can't hear me?
啊, 惨了!  凯撒, 它滑掉.
Ah, fuck!   Caesar, it slipped.
我打算准备一下.  你他妈怎么搞得?
I was trying to get ready.   How the fuck did you do that?
凯撒, 这是个意外, 我不小心的.
Caesar, it was an accident. I didn't mean to.
我再去买.  没时间了!
I'll get some more.   There's no fuckin' time!
别傻了. 大把时间呢.
Don't be silly. There's lots of time.
我会清理, 然后再你还没换好衣服前回来.
I'll clean this up and I'll be back before you're even dressed.
妈的, 维!
Fuck, Vi!
当你开门时, 我会在那等你.
When you open the door, I'll be there.
[ 维雅乐 ] 如果他看见你怎么办?
What if he sees you?
[ 克尔奇 ] 他不会的.
He won't.
你怎么就能那么确定?
You can't know for certain that he won't see you.
相信我吧.  我只是担心啊. 万一, 怎么办?
Trust me.   I'm just asking. What if?
如果他看到了...
If he does...
那我也没别的选择了, 对吧?
then I won't have a choice, will I?
当我进去时, 我会去拿钱.
When I'm inside, I'll get the money.
我需要一点东西来填满那公事包.
I'm gonna need something to fill the case.
把它藏在桌子附近.
Hide it near the desk.
然后...
And at that point...
就没得回头了.
there's no turning back.
当我拿到酒时...
When I get the scotch...
我怎么知道你会不会就那样溜了?
how do I know you won't just take off?
我也不知道你会不会去拿酒.
The same way I'll know that you went to go get the scotch.
互相信任.
Trust.
我还是不了解我怎么能不被怀疑...
I still don't see how I'm gonna get away clean...
钱是在我的房里啊.
with all the money in the apartment.
大家都会以为钱是我拿了.
Everyone's gonna think I took it.
凯撒不会.  为什么?
Not Caesar.   Why?
因为你要骗他.
'Cause of what you're gonna tell him.
要尽量骗的逼真点.
You gotta be as real as you can.
当你拿着酒走回去后...
The moment you walk through that door with the scotch...
你会当他们来过了.
you'll be covered.
那时刻是整个计划最重要的一缳.
That moment's the most important moment of the plan.
假如你演的够逼真的话, 他会相信的, 因为他内心...
'Cause if you're real enough, he's gonna believe you, 'cause deep down...
也是那么认为的.
he'll want to.
凯? 啊, 真对不起. 他们来早了.
C? Shit, I'm sorry. They were early.
你说什么?  他们刚走啊, 不是吗?
What are you talkin' about?   They just left, didn't they?
什么东西, 你醉啦?  你是说他们还没来?
What, are you drunk?   They weren't just up here?
没啊, 他们还在路上吧.
No, they're still on their way.
那不对啊.
That doesn't make any sense.
为什么?  我刚在楼下见到强尼.
Why?   I just saw Johnnie downstairs.
什么?
What?
是啊. 我下车时看见他在他的宝马里.
Yeah. I was getting out of my car, and I saw him in his BMW.
不对, 那不可能.  是他, 凯撒.
Nah, it couldn't have been.   It was him, Caesar.
我很肯定.
I'm positive.
维, 那是不可能的.
Vi, that's impossible.
凯撒, 我认得强尼.
Caesar, I know Johnnie.
那个是他.
It was him.
我也吓了一跳. 真不敢相信我错过了他们.
I screamed when I saw him. I couldn't believe I missed him.
我知道你会难过, 所以我想跟他们道歉...
I knew you were gonna be upset, so I thought I'd stop and apologize...
然后把酒给吉诺, 可是...
and give Gino the scotch, but...
我鸣了几次车笛, 可是他都好象没听见. 也没停车.
I honked a couple of times, and Johnnie didn't even hear me. He didn't stop.
可是...
But...
吉诺的飞机还有半小时才到啊.
Gino's plane doesn't get here for another half hour.
呃, 实际上我也没见到吉诺在车里.
Actually, I didn't see Gino in the car.
如果凯撒真的那么讨厌强尼, 那当他打开公事包时...
If Caesar hates Johnnie as much as you say, when he opens that case...
他将会相信是强尼嫁祸给他.
he's gonna know in his gut that Johnnie just fucked him.
他将会进退两难. 两个人他都惹不起.
He'll have no choice. He can't go after Gino or Johnnie.
他只有一个退路.
There's only one way out.
就是逃跑.
He'll have to run.
他若真的逃...
And if he runs...
每个人都会觉得是他拿了那些钱.
everyone will assume he took the money.
你不会有嫌疑, 而我们都会变的富有.
You'll be clean, and we'll be rich.
[ 维雅乐 ] 天啊, 太完美了.
Jesus, that's beautiful.
你真是非常聪明, 那你怎么会被抓呢?
If you're this goddamn smart, how did you ever get caught?
我曾经有个伙伴.
I had a partner once.
她出卖了我.
She fucked me.
我不会.
I won't.
拭目以待吧.
I think we're gonna find out.
哦, 天啊!  凯撒?
Oh, God!   Caesar?
不.
No.
[ 维雅乐 ] 凯?
C?
哦, 不.
Oh, no.
哦, 老天.
Oh, God.
[ 咒骂声 ]
维.
Vi.
维, 我被人算计了.
Vi, I've been set up.
强尼?
Johnnie?
那杂种!
That fuck!
那死杂种!
That rat fuck!
那狗娘养的死杂种!
That motherless rat fuck!
为什么? 强尼为什么要这么做?
Why? Why would Johnnie do this?
我的天啊. 维雅乐, 想想清楚.
Jesus Christ. Violet, open your fucking eyes.
强尼讨厌我正如我讨厌他那样.
Johnnie hates me as much as I hate him.
我痛恨那狗娘养的死杂种.
I hate that motherless rat fuck.
真他妈的恨他.  可是你知道是他干的啊.
I fuckin' hate him.   But you know he did it.
是啊. 可是? 我能怎样?
Yeah. So what? So fucking what?
你看, 钱没了, 对吗?
Look, the money is gone, right?
吉诺马上就要来拿了.
Gino's coming to get it.
你觉得他会相信我跟他说的...
Do you think Gino is going to believe me when I tell him...
他的小兔崽子偷了他的钱吗?
his little rat fuck son stole it?
换成是我也不会相信. 知道我在想什么吗?
'Cause I don't. You know what I think?
我马上就是个死人了. 跟死没两样了.
I'm a dead man. I'm one in the back of the head.
我只能这么想啊.
That's what I think.
那我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我知道强尼要我落跑.
I know what Johnnie wants me to do. Johnnie wants me to run.
他要我离开这里.
He wants me outta here.
可是假如我跑的话, 每个人都会认为是我干的...
But if I run, then everybody thinks I fucking did it...
然后那二百万他就袋的安稳了.
and he gets away with two million clean.
我可以想象现在的他...
I can see him right now...
在迎接吉诺的路上, 暗笑着我的下场.
on the way to get Gino, laughin' at me!
暗笑着我, 暗笑着我!
Laughin' at me, laughin' at me !
暗笑着我!
Laughin' at me!
他妈的暗笑着我的下场!
Fuckin' laughin' at me!
走开! 维雅乐, 让我冷静一下, 好吗?
Don't! Please. Don't touch me, okay?
我要好好想想. 把整件事想清楚!
I gotta think. I gotta fuckin' think this through!
凯撒, 我觉得我们应该赶紧离开.
Caesar, I think we should run.
现在就走吧, 免得来不及了!
We have to go now, before it's too late!
让开, 维雅乐, 让我冷静一下.
Please, Violet, leave me alone.
好吗?
Please, all right?
你他妈的让我一个人想一想!
Just leave me the fuck alone!
好吧, 凯撒.
All right, Caesar.
我要好好的想一想. 想个办法应付.
I gotta think, that's all. I just gotta think.
[ 电话铃声 ]
是我.  怎么了?
It's me.   What happened?
他疯了. 我从没见过他象现在这样.
He totally freaked out. I've never seen him like this.
他完全疯掉了.
He's out of his fucking mind.
不要紧的, 只要他相信是强尼干的就行了.
That's all right, as long as he believes it was Johnnie.
相信? 天啊!
Believes it? Jesus!
他就是因为这点发疯的. 他恨不得杀了他.
It's driving him crazy. He wants to kill him.
我不知道该怎么做, 克尔奇.
I don't know, Corky.
我现在很紧张. 不晓得他会做出什么事情来.
I'm getting really nervous. I don't know what he's gonna do.
不要紧的维雅乐. 计划很顺利.
It's all right, Violet. It's working.
现在我们只能等着看他怎么做.
All we gotta do is wait him out and see what he does.
万一他不逃怎么办?
What if he doesn't run?
那表示他会去杀强尼.
That means he'll probably kill Johnnie.
哦, 天呐! 我得赶紧离开!
Oh, Christ! I have to get out of here!
听好, 假如他不走, 你可以走.
Listen, if he doesn't run, all you gotta do is break down.
进去睡房假装收拾东西.
Go into the bedroom and pack some things.
一面哭一面对他说你爱他, 可是你不能再忍受了.
Start crying. Tell him you love him, but you can't take it.
你现在很怕, 所以你要离开, 然后就走出去.
You're sorry, but you gotta Ieave, and just waIk out.
好吧.
All right. Okay.
计划就快成功了, 撑着点.
We're almost there. Just hang on.
他来了!
He's coming!
我知道我该怎么做了. 我要把钱拿回来.
I know what I have to do. I have to get the money back.
钱? 不见了啊.
The money? The money's gone.
不, 不, 不, 强尼拿了. 我要去拿回来.
No, Johnnie's got it. I gotta get it back.
怎么找, 你不知道他收那去了.
It could be anywhere.
他不够时间的维雅乐.
There's not enough time, Violet.
他要去机场接吉诺对吧?
Johnnie's gotta pick up Gino at the airport, right?
[ 凯撒 ] 那说明钱现在还在他的车子里.
That means he's probably got the money with him in the car.
他没有看见你对吧?
Did he see you?
没有.
No.
好. 那很好.
Good. That's good.
那说明我现在有利了.
That means I got the edge.
他不知道我晓得了.
He doesn't know I know.
所以他把报纸放进公事包里去.
That's why he put the paper in the case.
他要我亲手交给吉诺.
He wants me to hand it to Gino.
假如我真那么做
Then there's no doubt I did it.
吉诺就会杀了我.
Gino will put a bullet in me himself.
可是那不会发生了.
But that's not gonna happen.
那白痴算计不了我的. 这种程度的计划难不倒我.
That jack off's not gonna set me up. No way. Not like this.
你疯了.
This is insane.
你要干嘛?
What are you doin'?
我要离开.
I'm leaving.
我不想搅进这趟浑水. 太可怕了.
I don't want any part of this shit. I don't want to be involved.
你不能走.  为什么不行.
You can't leave.   The hell I can't.
我需要你.  你根本不需要我.
I need you.   You don't need me.
你从来没需要过我.
You've never needed me.
我帮不了你啊, 明白吗?
I can't help you, understand?
我不能让你离开.
I can't let you leave.
假如你不跟我在一起, 我只有认定你也要跟我作对.
If you're not with me, I have to assume you're against me.
凯撒, 你真疯了.
Caesar, this is crazy.
也许吧, 也许没有.
Maybe it is. Maybe it isn't.
你也许不小心掉了那瓶酒.
Maybe you dropped that bottle of scotch by accident.
你也许是故意的.
Maybe you didn't.
你能够那么容易的...
I would've been so easy...
让他能溜进屋来.
to let him in as you left.
你怎么会那么想的.
You can't believe that.
我见过他色迷迷的望过你.
I've seen the way he looks at you.
他一直想要得到你.
He's always wanted you.
也许二百万让你昏了头.
Maybe two million bucks finally bought you.
对不起, 维雅乐.
I'm sorry, Violet.
我是想信你.
I wanna trust you.
可是你得明白.
But you understand.
我没有其他的选择.
I don't have any other choice.
你确定你不想喝点东西?
You sure you don't want a drink?
[ 弹动声 ]
[ 门铃声 ]
你好.  是啊, 我们终于到了.
Hello.   Yeah, we're here.
啊, 强尼.  开门啊.
Hey, Johnnie.   Open the fuckin' door.
好的. 上来吧.
Sure. Come on up.
吉诺.
Gino.
见到你真好. 维, 看看谁来了.
Good to see you. Vi, look who's here.
你好, 吉诺. 好久不见.
Hello, Gino. How are you?
嗨, 维雅乐.
你不该打我的.  你是不是还想继续.
You shouldn't have hit me.   You wanna get into this now?
不了, 凯撒, 现在不行.
No, Caesar, not now.
[ 笑声 ]
你永远都是那么迷人维雅乐.
You are as radiant as ever, Violet.
吉诺, 葛莱恩李维特, 是吗?
Gino, Glenlivet, right?
[ 意大利文 ]
我要跟维雅乐一样的饮料.
And I'll have whatever Violet's drinking.
我没喝东西.  哦, 那么, 我也不用了.
I'm not drinking.   Oh, well, then neither will I.
噢 不 我要 T&T.
No, I'll have a Tanqueray and tonic.
凯撒, 两杯 T&T's.
Caesar, two T&T's.
干杯? 来, 大家.
Salud, eh? Roy, Pop, Violet.
凯撒.
Caesar.
哦, 不行, 强尼.
Uh uh, no, no, Johnnie.
我要下注.  现在不准打电话.
I gotta make a bet.   No goddamn phone. Not now.
凯撒, 来这坐. 我们好好聊聊.
Cesare, come and sit. We're gonna talk now.
强尼, 你也是. 不是那边.
Johnnie, you too. No, no.
凯撒, 看着我.
Cesare, look at me.
强尼告诉了我事情的经过.
Johnnie, he said to me what happened.
凯撒, 帮我个忙好吗? 私人要求, 行吗?
Cesare, you gotta do me a favor. A personal favor for me, huh?
我想你应该开始象尊重我般尊重强尼, 好吗?
You gotta start respecting Johnnie the way you respect me.
[ 意大利文 ] 好, 好.
Good, good.
还有你强尼, 别再乱来.
And you, Johnnie, you gotta stop acting stupid.
你要凯撒尊重你就得用心的做事.
You gotta earn this respect that Cesare's gonna give.
[ 意大利文 ]
好!
Good!
搞定了!
Done!
现在...
Now...
我的钱在哪儿?
where's my money?
知道那家伙怎么动的手脚?
We know how this was done?
是的. 知道了.
Yeah. I know.
这种事不会再发生了?
And it won't happen again?
好. 搞定. 走吧.
Good. Done. We go now.
哦, 等等啊 老爸.
Wait a minute, Pop. Jesus Christ.
你还有两个小时飞机才起飞.
You got two hours till your plane leaves.
[ 吉诺用意大利文说话 ]
放轻松吧. 来多一杯.
Just relax. Have a drink.
[ 继续说意大利文 ] 凯撒, 葛莱恩李维特.
Caesare, Glenlivet
那, 凯撒, 告诉我
So, Caesar, tell me something.
总数是多少.
What did it total out at?
2.176. 2.176.\n2.176.
[ 口哨声 ] 难以置信.
Unbelievable.
你能相信吗, 维雅乐?
Can you believe that, Violet?
强尼. [ 意大利文 ]
Johnnie.
我只想知道一件事.
I just wanna know one thing.
就一件事.
Just one thing after he made such a big deal about it.
应该无所谓吧, 凯撒?
I'll bet it wasn't such a big deal, huh, Caesar?
什么事呢, 强尼?
What's that, Johnnie?
钱啊.
The money.
我觉得把那些钱弄干净...
I'll bet it wasn't nothin' to make it clean...
也没多大难题.
after you made such a big fuckin' deal about it.
我跟你说过什么  这对我很重要, 爸.
What I tell you     It's important to me, Pop.
这个简单的问题, 他答了, 就没事了.
It's a simple question. If he'd answer it, that's the end of it.
你想说什么, 强尼?
Where's this goin', Johnnie?
承认吧.
Just admit it.
承认什么?
Admit what?
你过份紧张那些钱!
That you overreacted!
你弄不见的! 不是我.
You lost it! Not me.
是你的错误.
It was your mistake.
你想这么说?
You wanna play it this way?
不如听听我说.
I could play it this way.
你想知道谁犯下错误?
You wanna know who made a mistake?
打开公事包.
Open the case.
凯撒.  闭嘴, 维雅乐.
Caesar.   Shut up, Violet.
这是我跟强尼之间的事.
This is between me and Johnnie.
你不是要有个答复?
You wanna do this now?
动手吧.
Let's do it.
打开这箱子.
Open the fuckin' case.
打开它.
Open the case.
钥匙呢?
Where's the fucking key?
你还需要钥匙吗?
You don't need a key.
那我要怎么打开它?
Then how the fuck can I open it?
你刚刚怎么开现在就怎么开.
The same way you did before.
你在胡说些什么?
What are you talking about?
[ 叹气声 ]
好吧, 强尼.
All right, Johnnie.
维雅乐...
Violet...
帮我倒多杯酒来.
get me another drink.
这是什么?  你跟我坐好!
What is this?   Don't you fucking move!
[ 意大利文 ]  他妈的, 在那里?
Where is it, fuckface?
什么在那里?  钱啊!
Where's what?   The money!
好吧, 凯撒, 不不知道你怎么想的 但是你先把枪放下
Okay, Caesar, if you don't put down that gun
坐下.
Sit down.
凯撒, 这是什么?
Caesar, what is this?
吉诺, 你儿子偷了你的钱来陷害我.
Gino, your son stole this money to set me up!
他偷了你的钱, 我有证人!
He fuckin' stole it, and I can prove it!
维雅乐, 告诉他们.
Violet, tell them.
告诉他们!
Tell them!
强尼, 说吧.
For God's sake, Johnnie, do what he says.
我的天! 这是怎么一回事.
For Christ's sake! This isn't happening.
下一枪就打断你的命根子.
Next one blows off your fuckin' dick!
你马上就是个死人了 你快死了!
I'm looking at a dead man. You're a fuckin' dead man!
够了!
Enough!
吉诺, 坐下.  你竟敢用枪指着我?
Gino, don't.   Do you point the gun at me?
你忘了我是谁? 我是吉诺麻钟尼!
Do you know who I am? I am Gino Marzzone!
除非你是傻瓜, 把枪给我!
哦, 吉诺, 千万不要.
No, Gino, please.
把枪给我.
吉诺, 坐下.
Gino, sit down.
我们是一家人, 凯撒.
We're family, Cesare.
家人, 凯撒.
Family, Caesar.
家人.
Family.
现在...
Now...
把它给我.
give it to me.
乖孩子.
Good man.
[ 枪声 ]
[ 痛呼声 ]
别开枪.
Don't shoot.
[ 扳动声 ]
我是被逼的, 维雅乐.
I had to do it, Violet.
你看见了, 我没别的选择.
You saw it. I had no choice.
是强尼敢的.
It was Johnnie.
满嘴谎言的混蛋. 他逼我的.
Lying rat fuck. He made me do it.
喂! 喂!
Hey! Hey!
笨蛋东西! 你以为你能陷害我? 是吗?
You stupid fuck! You think you could set me up? Huh?
我是个死人吗强尼? 我是死人?
I'm a dead man, Johnnie? I'm a fucking dead man?
猜猜看强尼. 谁死了啊? 谁啊?
Guess again, Johnnie. Who's the dead man? Who?
谁死了, 杂种? 谁? 谁?
Who's dead, fuckface? Who? Who?
我听不见强尼, 再猜啊.
I can't hear you, Johnnie. Guess again.
再猜多一次强尼, 再猜啊!
Take another guess, Johnnie. Take another fuckin' guess.
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
也许三个小时吧.
Maybe three hours.
凯撒, 你想干嘛?
Caesar, what are you going to do?
你觉得呢? 我们当然是把钱给拿回来了.  什么?
We're gonna get the money back.   What?
维雅乐, 如果把钱拿回来后, 这一切都好必没发生过.
Violet, if we get the money back, then none of this ever happened.
凯撒, 你刚杀了吉诺麻钟尼.
Caesar, you just killed Gino Marzzone.
错, 我没有. 没尸体的话我就没杀人了.
No, I didn't. Not if the bodies disappear.
假如钱在这. 可他们没出现.
Not if the money's here. Then they never showed up.
他们发生什么事了?
What happened to them?
我不知道. 也许我们永远不知道.
I don't know. Maybe we'll never know.
天哦, 还真是幸运.
My guess, it was a job.
也许是卡佩拉吧. 全是生意的一部分.
Maybe the Carpella's. All part of the business.
一旦我们找到钱后, 什么事情都没有了.
Look, once we find the money, then everything's gonna be all right.
[ 警笛声 ]
有人来了.
Somebody's coming.
[ 警笛声持续着 ]
去他妈的!  哦, 不.
Fuck!   Oh, no.
妈的!
Fuck!
凯撒, 我们该怎么办?
Caesar, what are we gonna do?
只是警察吧了. 尽量拖延时间.
They're just cops. Stall 'em as long as you can.
[ 嘀咕声 ]
[ 嘀咕声持续着 ]
吉诺, 天啊.
Gino, man.
[ 凯撒 ] 来吧, 来吧!
Come on. Come on!
[ 叹气声 ]
[ 门铃声 ]
应门啊.
Answer it.
[ 门铃持续着 ]
你好?  哦 夫人, 我们是警察.
Hello?   This is the police, ma'am.
警察?
The police?
我们接到消息说这里有枪战. 麻烦你让我们进去一下.
We had a report of gunfire. Can you buzz us in, please?
枪战? 开什么玩笑?  不是说笑的夫人.
Gunfire? Is this a joke?   No joke, ma'am.
开门吧.  呃.
Please open the door.   Um.
我怎么知道你是真的警察?
How do I know that you're really the police?
夫人, 你必须开门啊.
Ma'am, you have to open the door.
好吧.
All right.
[ 嘀咕声 ]
[ 电梯铃声 ]
[ 枪战 ]  [ 叹气生 ]
[ 敲门声 ]
如果你想干些蠢事...
Now, if you're thinking about doing something stupid...
记得, 我刚杀了吉诺麻钟尼.
remember, I just killed Gino Marzzone.
了解吗?
You understand what that means?
他们只是警察.
They're just cops.
看见啦? 我们是真警察.
See? We're for real.
对不起. 常有贼扮警察的事件.
I'm sorry. It's just that sometimes you hear stories.
没事, 你所做的是对的.
You did the right thing.
进来吧.
Come on in.
你们好啊, 芝加哥的治安维护者.
Hey, hey! Chicago's finest.
怎么样两位? 今晚有什么大事吗?
How's it going tonight, fellas?
还好, 你呢?
Very good, sir?
对不起, 我耳朵有点毛病. 听觉有些问题.
I'm sorry. I got a bum ear. Can't hear shit with it.
我是凯撒, 这是我女朋友维雅乐.
My name is Caesar, and this here is my Violet.
那么, 她说你们听到有枪战?
So, Violet tells me there's some problems about gunshots.
嗯是的. 附近的一个邻居报的警.
Uh, yes, sir. A neighbor in the building called in.
我觉得我们知道发生了什么事.  大概就是电视机吧.
I think we know what happened.   Probably just the television.
喔, 电视机的声音啊.
Oh, the television.
甜心, 麻烦你把电视机关了.
Honey, why don't you turn it off?
类似的情况常有.
This happened before.
这耳朵, 一出世就如此的了.
This ear, I was born with it.
助听器的电池用完了, 对不起啊  [ 电视声停止 ]
The batteries went dead on my hearing aid. I'm sorry.
没关系的  别担心.
It's all right.   No big deal.
真是不好意思. 喝不喝啤酒?
I hate to trouble you guys. Can I get you a beer?
哦不了, 当值中. 不能喝.
Uh, no. Not on duty. Sorry.
嗯, 可以借用下洗手间吗?
But, uh, do you mind if I use your bathroom?
当然没问题. 就在那边.
No. Sure. It's right over here.
谢了.
Thanks.
嗯 那我要弄点东西喝, 你们随便吧.
Listen, do you mind if I make myself a drink?
是的, 就在那.
Yeah, right there.
好的, 谢谢.
Sure. Go right ahead, sir.
[ 警官叹气 ]
这地方真不错.
This is a beautiful place.
谢谢.
Thank you.
这里到底是不是公寓?
Is this a condo?
好, 走吧.
Okay, let's roll.
喔, 对了记得要多买点备用电池好吗?
Oh, try to keep extra batteries around for the aid, okay?
这主意不错.
Good idea.
[ 凯撒 ] 来吧. 我们走.
Come on. Let's go.
妈的.
Shit.
妈的! 到底在哪儿?
Fuck! Where is it?
想想.
Think.
肯定是在他家了.
It's gotta be at his place.
上车.
Get in the car.
凯撒, 我觉得  我说上车!
Caesar, I don't think     Get in the fucking car!
二百万啊, 克尔奇.
Two million dollars, Corky.
[ 凯撒 ] 二百万. 一定在这儿的. 一定在的.
Two million dollars. It's gotta be here. It's gotta be.
我要冷静, 想想强尼会怎么想.
I just   I gotta think. Think Iike Johnnie.
好, 我是强尼的话.
Okay, I'm Johnnie.
我一走进来.
I come in.
我会放那呢?
Where did I put it?
这是一笔大数目, 我要把它收好.
That's a Iot of fuckin' money, and I gotta hide it.
我要把它藏起来, 我没多少时间.
I gotta hide it. I don't have much time.
我要去机场接我老爸!
I gotta get to the airport, pick up my fuckin' daddy!
[ 玻璃被敲破声 ]
我恨不得看看凯撒着急的脸.
I can't wait to see Caesar's face when he finds out.
他会放那呢?  凯.
Where did he put it?   C.
想啊, 想啊.
Think. Think.
在那里, 你他妈的?
Where is it, you motherfucker?
在那里? 在那里?
Where? Where?
[ 抽泣 ]
凯?
C?
凯.
C.
不在这, 凯撒.
It's not here, Caesar.
会在那里?
Where is it?
不知道. 怎么知道他会把它藏到那里去了.
I don't know. It could be anywhere.
我们也不知道他是不是单身一个人.
We don't even know if he was alone, Caesar.
来吧. 我们该离开了.
Come on. We have to get out of here.
我们没多少时间了.
We don't have much time.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
要弄多些时间. 多点时间.
Gotta buy more time. More time.
你要打给谁呢?
Who are you gonna call?
喂?  啊, 米奇.
Yeah?   Hey, Mickey.
哦天.
Oh, God.
凯撒, 你他妈知道现在几点了吗?
Caesar, what the fuck time is it?
哦, 米奇对不起吵醒了你. 我知道现在很晚了.
Oh, Mickey, did I wake you up? Listen, I'm sorry. I know it's late.
可是他们人还没来, 我有点担心.
I don't know if this is a big deal, but they ain't showed up yet.
什么? 他们还没来?
What? They ain't there?
嗯. 我打电话去机场问过了. 飞机没误点.
No. I I I called the airport. The plane landed on time.
我也打给了强尼, 可是那里没人听.
I even called over at Johnnie's house, but there was no answer there.
好, 那我帮你打听打听. 看看我能帮上忙吗.
Okay. Let me call around. I'll see what I can do.
别乱走, 留在家.
Don't go anywhere, okay?
好的. 我会的.
Yeah, okay, sure.
凯撒, 钱还安全吧?
Caesar, you still have the money?
当然了米奇, 钱在我这儿.
Oh, yeah, Mickey, I still got the money.
正在看着它们呢.
Starin' right at it.
好. 等等吧, 我会再打给你的.
Good. Sit tight. I'll call you.
晚安.
Bye.
那我开始收拾东西, 你知道该怎么做的了.
So I'll start packing. You know what you have to do.
我会用强尼的车把尸体丢进河里去.
I'll use Johnnie's car to dump the bodies in the lake.
我需要垃圾袋, 绳子跟胶带.
I need plastic bags, rope and tape.
快点.
Just hurry.
克尔奇, 听电话.
Please, Corky, please.
谢谢老天.  我还在这里.
Thank God.   I'm still here.
我真怕你会离我而去.
I was so afraid you were going to leave me.
你没出卖我, 我也不会出卖你的.
You don't quit on me, Violet. I won't quit on you.
克尔奇, 成功了. 他好象要开始逃了.
Corky, it worked. He's going to run.
他需要一些时间来处理那些尸体...
He needs to take care of the bodies to buy himseIf a little time...
但当他离开后, 这一切都结束了.
but as soon as he leaves, it's over.
再等多一阵子.
Just a little while longer.
克尔奇...
Corky...
我要告诉你一些东西.
I want to tell you something.
我知道, 维雅乐.
I know, Violet.
我知道.
I know.
那是我留下来的原因.
It's why I'm still here.
那是谁?
Who was that?
维, 那是谁?
Vi, who the fuck was that?
你打了给米奇? 你是不是打了给米奇?
Did you call Mickey? Did you call Mickey?
是不是!
Did you!
米奇, 是你吗?
Mickey, is that you?
妈的.
Fuck.
[ 电话铃声 ]
[ 电话铃声持续着 ]
那是谁? 谁在隔壁?
Who is that? Who's over there?
谁在隔壁? 告诉我! 告诉我!
Who's over there? Tell me! Tell me!
不要! 住手! 凯撒! 凯撒!
No! Stop! Caesar! Caesar!
[ 维雅乐 惨叫 ]
不! 不! 不要! 凯撒!
No! No! No! Caesar!
[ 惨叫 ]
把枪放下否则我开枪.
Drop the fucking gun or die.
放下!
Drop it!
转过身来.
Turn around.
你?
You?
他妈的, 活见鬼.
Holy fucking Christ.
你是在他妈的跟我开玩笑吧.
You gotta be fucking kiddin' me.
[ 凯撒 ] 你是在他妈的跟我开玩笑吧.
喂!
Hey!
起来!
Come on!
起来. 起来.
Wake up. Wake up.
起来, 你这贱人.
Wake up, you fucking dyke.
好.
Good.
我现在知道一切了.
I know everything now.
我不想听什么"我不知道"的废话, 明白吗?
So I don't wanna hear any "I don't know" bullshit, understand?
靠, 我第一眼见到你时就该知道会有这么一天.
God, I shouId've seen this coming the minute I met you.
大家都知道你是那种不能被信任的人.
Everybody knows your kind can't be trusted.
烂货, 看到你我就反感.
Fuckin' queers. You make me sick.
你犯了个致命的错误.
But you made a fatal mistake.
就是算计错人了...
You tried to fuck the wrong guy...
我可以跟你打包票...
and I swear to you...
我一定会杀了你.
I'm gonna kill you for it.
我的钱呢?
Where's my money?
别告诉他. 他不会杀你的.
Don't tell him. He can't kill you.
维雅乐.  暂时不会, 拿到钱后就难说了.
Violet.   Not until he has the money.
钱在哪儿?
Now, where is it?
舔我.
Lick me.
我 的 钱 在 那 里 ?
Where is my money?
杀了我, 要不就把枪拿开.
Either pull the trigger, or get that fucking thing out of my face.
臭婊子.
Fuckin' cunt.
凯撒, 冷静用脑想想.
Caesar, stop acting like an asshole and think.
维雅乐, 别告诉我怎么做.
Violet, don't try to tell me what to do.
你和我们一样需要那笔钱.
You need the money just like we do.
闭嘴!  放我们走. 万事好商量.
Shut up!   Let us go. We'll make a deal.
你他妈的闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
你把她给怎么了, 啊?
What did you do to her, huh?
你他妈的把她给怎么了, 啊?
What did you fuckin' do to her?
这个不是我的维雅乐!
That's not my Violet!
她对你做了些什么?
What did she do to you?
很多你办不到的事情.
Everything you couldn't.
你这不知感恩的婊子.
You ungrateful fuckin' bitch.
没遇见我之前你可是一无所有的.
Vi, you were nothing before you met me.
难道你忘了? 你什么都没有.
Don't you remember? You had nothing.
谁给了你这个地方住, 啊?
Who gave you this place, huh?
谁给你的?
Who gave it to you?
是我啊, 是我!
I did, Vi. I did.
你什么也不是, 什么也没有.
You were nothing. You had nothing.
那么多废话. 看看你自己吧, 凯撒.
What a load of crap. Take a look at yourself, Caesar.
你也不过是个小混混. 替黑帮洗黑钱.
You're nothing but a common thug. You launder money for the Mob.
租女人就象租这房子一样.
You rent women like you rented this apartment.
你利用了我, 正如我利用了你一样.
You used me, Caesar. That's all. Just like I used you.
全部的生意.
All part of the business.
你出卖了我.
You betrayed me.
你杀了吉诺.
You murdered Gino.
当然了, 你害的我那样做的. 我是被逼的.
Yeah, sure. You made me. I had to do that.
放屁! 你自己干的.
Bullshit! You did it.
你不甘心被强尼陷害所以你杀了他们.
You did it because you couldn't stand the thought of Johnnie fucking you.
闭嘴.  你闭嘴.
Shut up.   You shut up.
好吧, 维雅乐. 好吧!
All right, Violet. All right!
你要那些钱? 全部的钱?
You want the business, Violet? All of the business?
我会给你的. 我会全部给你.
I'll fucking give it to you. I'll give you all of it.
我会让你痛苦的.
I'm gonna make you fuckin' suffer.
就好象雪丽一样. 就好象他妈的雪丽一样.
Just like Shelly, Violet. Just like fuckin' Shelly.
对不起, 克尔奇.
I'm sorry, Corky.
别说傻话. 来帮我.
Don't be sorry. Help me.
哦, 不, 不, 不, 不!
Oh, no, no, no!
[ 嘀咕声 ]
嗯 维, 记得这个吗?
Hey, Vi, do you remember these?
好, 我将由维雅乐开始.
All right, I'm gonna start with Violet.
[ 呻吟 ]
好让你知道是怎么一回事.
So you get an idea of what's comin'.
我会问你十个问题.
I'm gonna ask you ten questions.
每当我得不到答案时...
Every time I don't get an answer...
我会剪掉她一支手指.
I cut off a finger.
[ 呻吟持续着 ]
钱在那里?
Where's the money?
[ 门铃响 ]
是米奇.
It's Mickey.
我刚问说:"钱在那里?"
I said, "Where's the money?"
[ 维雅乐 呻吟 ]  好吧, 我告诉你.
All right, I'll tell you.
在隔壁房子里.
It's in the apartment next door.
我把它放进油漆桶里.
I put it in the paint drums.
好. 现在, 我说过我会杀了你的, 记得吗?
Good. Now, I promised you I wouId kill you. Remember?
你不可以杀我.
You can't kill me.
哦? 为什么?
Oh, really? Why not?
我可能在说谎.
I could be lying.
你会后悔你那么说的.
You're gonna be sorry you said that.
[ 电梯声响 ]
他娘的!
Motherfucker!
狗娘养的.
Son of a bitch.
钥匙, 钥匙, 钥匙, 钥匙.
Keys, keys, keys, keys.
[ 呻吟 ]
[ 敲门声 ]
你要的话, 我可以现在马上杀了你,
I can kill you right now, if that's what you want.
还是你选择继续生存.
Or you can live.
那你就得帮我.
But I need your help.
你得帮我让米奇相信一切事情都正常.
You gotta help me make Mickey believe that everything is normal.
现在, 你想怎么办?
Now, what do you wanna do?
想生存吗?
Do you wanna live?
[ 开琐声 ]
哦! 天啊!
Oh! Oh, shit!
真是的! 米奇, 你吓死我了.
Christ! Mickey, you scared the shit out of me.
你们怎么了? 怎么都拿着枪啊?
What are you guys doin' with your peckers in your hand?
你要杀我吗米奇?
You gonna do me, Mickey?
不是, 刚刚没人应门, 我担心你有事.
No. There was no answer.
难怪我好象听到有人敲门.
I thought I heard some knocking at the door.
我按了电铃, 敲了门...
I was buzzing, I was knocking...
不过我想你在浴室里听不见吧.
but I guess you couldn't hear me on account of being in the shower.
是啊米奇, 我太紧张了.
Yeah, well, you know, Mick, I'm all wound up.
我为了吉诺的事几乎疯掉, 所以...
I'm driving myself crazy over this Gino thing, and, well...
维, 她想说...
Vi, you know, she thought maybe...
让我在浴室里放松放松
she could, you know, relax me in the
维雅乐是个好女人.
That Violet is one nice lady.
我也希望有人能让我放轻松.
I wish someone would help me relax.
呵呵, 喝点什么?
Uh, let me get you guys a drink, huh?
我要思考兹, 你呢?
I got scotch, whatever you want.
我们很担心你呢, 凯.
We was worried about you.
我? 为什么?
Me? Why?
我们去了强尼家, 想查查看.
We went over to Johnnie's place, just to check it out.
没想到那里被人破坏的很利害.
It was busted up, bad.
什么?
What?
所以我在想可能是以为那笔钱而来的.
Started thinking maybe it's about the money.
我打了电话给你, 可是一直不通.
So I call you, but all I got is the busy signal.
我想说可能是电话掉了, 就赶紧飞奔来了.
I figure the phone is off the hook. That's why I come rushing over here.
哦, 那电话. 真是的, 是我弄的,
Fuck, the phone. Shit. That was me. I did that.
妈的! 不应该那样做的, 对不起.
Fuck! That was a stupid thing to do, huh?
没事, 假如维雅乐是在帮我放松...
Hey, if Violet was helping me relax...
我也会做同样的事.
I'd probably do the same thing.
噢 凯, 我有件事想问你.
Hey, Caes, can I ask you something?
说吧.
Sure.
你怎么把家具都重新排列过了呢?
Why did you move all the furniture around?
让我猜猜.
Let me guess.
那应该也是维雅乐的意思.
That was Violet's idea too.
是的, 呃, 其实...
Yeah, uh, actually...
她对于吉诺的到来很紧张...
she was nervous about Gino comin'...
想说一切都要尽善尽美
and wanted everything to look perfect and
你知道女人的啦, 米奇.
You know women, Mick.
当然啦 凯, 她们会令男人干蠢事, 对吧?
Sure, Caes. They make us do stupid things, don't they?
那就是钱吗?  是的, 就是那个.
Is that the money?   Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
总数是多少啊?
What did it total out at?
2.176. 2.176\n2.176.
雪丽那王八蛋.
That fuckin' Shelly.
想说交给那帮家伙就没事了, 谁知道...
Gotta hand it to the guy, but, Jesus...
如果我是他我会在很早以前就逃了.
if I were him, I would've bailed a long time ago.
一个人用的着那么多钱吗?
I mean, how much money does a man need?
我还记得当时我在看这这笔钱.
I remember, I was just staring at all this goddamn money.
雪丽是跪着的...
Shelly went down on his knees...
强尼突然朝他头开了一枪.
and the next thing I know, Johnnie just blows his head off.
搞的满地一蹋糊涂.
What a fuckin' mess.
强尼还在不停的笑...
Johnnie's laughing his ass off...
凯撒就是在那时控制不住自己的.
and that's when Caesar lost it.
完了"乓"的一声.
And boom.
凯撒打了他.
He cold cocked him.
他打了那王八强尼麻钟尼.
He cold cocks fuckin' Johnnie Marzzone.
[ 笑声 ]
喂, 凯撒.
Hey, Caesar.
钥匙呢?
Where's the key?
呃, 钥匙
Um, the key
哦, 在我裤子里, 放在浴室了.
Oh, they're in my pants in the bathroom.
哦, 去他的. 我用不着钥匙.
Ah, fuck it. I don't need the key.
我不用钥匙都能进来, 不是吗?
I didn't need a key to get in here, did I?
[ 吞口水状 ]
[ 电话响 ]
那会是谁呢?  [ 电话铃声持续 ]
Who the hell could that be?
你不接听吗?
Are you gonna answer it?
要的.
Yeah.
喂?  [ 维雅乐 ] 嗨, 凯撒.
Hello?   Hello, Caesar.
这是吉诺.  啥?
This is Gino.   What?
你在自寻死路, 笨蛋. 假装我是吉诺.
You're blowing your only chance, asshole. Act like I'm Gino.
感谢老天! 我们都在担心你啊, 吉诺.
Holy Christ! We've been worried sick about you, Gino.
好孩子.  是吉诺.
Good boy.   It's Gino.
他们在那里?  我们遇到了一起车祸.
Where the hell is he?   We were in a car accident.
他们遇到了车祸.  幸好大家都没事.
They were in a car accident.   But everybody's all right.
大家都没事, 只是撞伤了而已.
Everybody's all right. Just bruises and shit.
真他妈的难以置信. 那些高速公路巡逻人员都死那去了.
Un fucking believabIe. I called those highway patrols. Dumb fucks.
米奇, 拜托别吵我听不是很清楚.
Mick, please. I'm trying to hear Gino.
听我说, 混蛋. 我知道你的枪现在在吧台那里.
Now you listen to me, asshole. I know your gun is behind the bar.
我们现在来个交易, 否则我就叫米奇来.
Either we make a deal right now, or I hand this phone to Mickey.
我在听.
I'm listening.
好. 我要属于我的东西. 那一半的钱.
All right. I want what's mine. I want half the money.
我们把米奇干掉, 可是不准杀克尔奇.
We get rid of Mickey, and no one else dies.
明白了吗? 说,"我是的, 我明白了."
No one. Say, "Yes, I understand."
是的, 我明白了.
Yes, I understand.
告诉他们我在肯尼迪附近的圣.玛丽那里.
Tell them I'm at St. Mary's off the Kennedy in the waiting room.
拿着电话直到我走出来为止.
Stay on the phone until I come out.
好的, 是.
Okay. Right.
肯尼迪附近的圣.玛丽那里.
St. Mary's off the Kennedy.
是的.
Yeah.
强尼没事吧?
Johnnie's okay?
米奇? 你怎么会在这里?
Mickey? What are you doing here?
维雅乐, 吉诺与强尼遇到了车祸.
Violet, it's Gino and Johnnie. They were in a car accident.
哦老天! 大家没事吧?
Oh, my God! Is everybody all right?
我想没事的.  好, 拜拜.
I think everything's okay.   All right. Bye.
他们在圣.玛丽那里, 真难以置信.
They're at St. Mary's. Can you fucking believe this?
我的车子坐不了那么多人, 给我你的车匙.
I can't fit them all in my car, so give me your keys.
当然.  你驾我的车吧.
Sure.   You drive my car.
维! 维!
Vi! Vi!
帮我个忙. 去浴室里拿我的钥匙, 在我裤子里.
Do me a favor. Go in my pants in the bathroom and get my keys.
来吧, 要走了. 维, 走了!
Come on. Let's go. Vi, let's go!
谢了, 维.  一到了马上打电话给我.
Thanks, V.   Call me as soon as you get there.
记得把电话放好.
Leave your phone on the hook.
呵呵, 这就是团队精神.
Now, that's teamwork.
我真该让他们把你给杀掉的.
I should've let 'em kill you.
他会把你也给杀了.
He would've done you too.
我就知道你不是个能信任的人.
I knew I couldn't trust you.
放心. 我说过不会杀你...
Relax. I said I would let you live...
就不会杀你的.
and I will.
也可能会.
Maybe.
走, 去看看你的姘头有没有说谎.
Let's go see if your dyke was dumb enough to lie.
走吧.
Let's go.
[ 呻吟 ]
好.
Yes.
不!
No!
维雅乐!
Violet!
维雅乐! 维雅乐!
Violet! Violet!
维雅乐!
Violet!
别这样, 好吗.
Come on, please.
[ 呼叫声 ]
婊子! 你他妈的婊子!
Bitch! You fuckin' bitch!
米奇?  维雅乐?
Mickey?   Violet?
哦上帝, 米奇. 他逼我这么做的.
Oh, God, Mickey. He made me do it.
我很怕. 我不想的, 米奇.
I was so afraid. I didn't want to, Mickey.
全是凯撒逼我的, 他逼我说谎.
It was Caesar, all Caesar. He made me help him.
你一定要帮我啊. 天啊!, 天啊!, 他来了!
You have to help me. Oh, God! Oh, God, he's coming!
克尔奇?
Corky?
哦, 他妈的.
Oh, fuck.
[ 呼叫声 ]
[ 嘀咕声 ]
停止!
Stop!
哦, 开什么玩笑.
Oh, for Christ's sakes.
结束了, 凯撒.
It's over, Caesar.
我打给了米奇. 他回着来了.
I called Mickey. He's on his way.
离开这里, 凯撒.
Get out of here, Caesar.
如果你想活下去, 现在就离开吧!
If you want to live, you'd better start running.
这么多年了你还不了解我吗.
All these years, and you still don't know me.
但是我了解你.
But I know you.
凯撒, 别逼我.
Caesar, don't.
你会怎么样? 开枪打我?
What are you gonna do with that, Vi? Shoot me?
你会杀了我吗? 别说笑了.
Kill me in cold blood? I don't think so.
如果你要杀我, 你早就开枪了.
If you were gonna shoot me, Vi, you'd have done it a long time ago.
如果我是你, 早在把钱拿回家时我就会杀了我
If I were you, I'd have shot me the minute I brought the money back.
可你没有, 让我告诉你为什么你没那么做.
But you didn't, and I'llI tell you why.
你不想开枪打我的.
You don't want to shoot me, Vi.
对吧?
Do you?
我知道你不敢的.
I know you don't.
凯撒, 你什么都不知道.
Caesar, you don't know shit.
[ 枪声 ]
[ 维雅乐 ] 我不明白米奇. 你怎么不报警?
I'll never understand it, Mickey. You didn't even call the police.
告诉过你了. 家族不要警察插手.
I told you. The family doesn't want the police around.
我们要自己料理这些事.
We want to take care of it ourselves, and we will.
我会找到他的, 我发誓.
I'll find him. I swear I will.
我知道你会的.
I know you will.
你确定你会没事?
Sure you're gonna be okay?
我是想说, 假如你改变主意的话...
I mean, if you're having second thoughts...
你随时可以来找我.
my offer still stands.
谢了米奇, 我受够这些了.
Thanks, Mickey, but I have to get out.
我只想离开这一切.
You know, I have to get away from all this.
不过, 非常谢谢你.
But thanks.
谢谢你帮我做了那么多.
Thanks for everything.
喂.  喂.
Hey.   Hey.
嗯, 进行的怎样了?
So, how'd it go?
我还在这, 不是吗?  嗯嗯.
I'm here, aren't I?   Mm hmm.
[ 车琐声 ]
嗯, 我觉得我们有需要一辆逃走的车.
Well, I thought we might need a getaway car.
嗯.
Hmm.
[ 启动引擎声 ]
你知道你跟我的分别吗?
You know what the difference is between you and me, Violet?.
不知道.
No
呵呵, 我也不知道.
Me, neither.
*  Well, she's all you'd ever want *
*  She's the kind I'd like to flaunt and take to dinner *
*  She's a lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  Talkin' about that little lady *
*  And the lady is mine *
*  But she's never in the way *
*  Always something nice to say What a blessing *
*  I can leave her on her own *
*  Knowing she's okay alone and there's no messin' *
*  She's a lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  Talkin' about that little lady *
*  And the lady is mine *
*  No she never asks very much *
*  And I don't abuse her *
*  Always treat her with respect *
*  I never would abuse her *
*  What's she's got is hard to find *
*  And I don't want to lose her *
*  Help me build a mountain from a little pile of clay *
*  But she's knows what I'm about *
*  She can take what I dish out *
*  And that's not easy *
*  But she knows me through and through *
*  And she knows just what to do *
*  And how to please me *
*  She's a lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  Talkin' about the little lady *
*  And the lady is mine *
*  She's a lady *
*  Ooh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  Listen to me people, she's a lady *
*  Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's a lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  Talkin' about the little lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
*  She's a lady *
*  Hey, yeah, yeah, she's a lady *
*  Oh, oh, oh, she's a lady *
*  I can't live without *
[ 电视声, 惊叫声, 嘀咕声 ]
[ 电视声持续着 ]